Preliminary Guide to the Lisner Auditorium records, 1946-2005 RG0055
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Office records, 1946-1952; RG0055 Series 4; 0.25 Linear feet (Box 1)
  - Autographed letter signed, Mary F. Martin, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Undated letter supporting racial segregation of Lisner Auditorium.
  - Typed letter, A Segregationalist, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Typed letter signed, Irene Palus, 10/31/1946 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Letter supporting racial segregation of Lisner Auditorium.
  - Typed letter signed, J.C. Thomas, 10/31/1946 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Autographed letter signed, Louise T. Williams, 11/15/1946 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Typed letter, McClain B. Smith, 11/15/1946 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Typed letter, Jean Williams, 11/15/1946 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Typed letter, Phyllis King, 11/15/1946 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Autographed letter signed, D. Gardiner, 11/22/1946 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Typed letter signed, Dorothy C. Bernard, 12/09/1946 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Typed letter signed, Ruth Smith, 07/01/1946 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Letter deploring racial segregation of Lisner Auditorium.
  - Typed letter signed, Arnold O. Abbott, 10/28/1946 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Letter deploring racial segregation of Lisner Auditorium from Chairman of The American Veterans Committee.
  - Typed letter signed, Dena B. Comarow, 01/16/1947 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Letter deploring racial segregation of Lisner Auditorium from Secretary-Treasurer of the Southwest Unit of the League of Women Shoppers.
  - Typed letter signed, Irving and Leah L. Feingold, 02/05/1947 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Autographed letter signed, B. F. Reiner, 02/05/1947 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Typed letter signed, Charlotte Orton, 02/05/1947 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Autographed letter signed, Jack W. Cohen, 02/06/1947 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Typed letter signed, Ethel Jean Davis, 02/06/1947 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Typed letter signed, Rose S. Messinger, 02/07/1947 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Flyer entitled "Music Hath Charms", 1947 ca. (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Flyer from The American Veterans Committee deploring racial segregation of Lisner Auditorium, with hand-written comment from a pro-segregatioanlist.
  - Held Over: Discrimination, 1947 ca. (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Photocopy of an article from The Amercian Veterans Committee recounting the Lisner controversy.
  - Telegram, 12/03/1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    From Branch 482 of IWO deploring racial segregation of Lisner Auditorium.
  - Newspaper editorials, 11/08/1946-08/09/1948 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Nine editorials from newpapers commenting on the racial segregation of Lisner Auditorium.
  - Trustees actions, 02/14/1946-02/14/1952 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Typed excerpts from Board of Trustees minutes relating to use of Lisner Auditorium.
- Posters, 1967-1992; RG0055 Series 5; .5 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2)
  This series consists of 58 performance posters from Lisner Auditorium. They range in date from 1967-92.
  Formerly ACC#159
  - Fall 1991 Program Board Film Festival (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dance Theater of Harlem, 03/24/1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Nigeria National Dance Troupe, 07/11/1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Odetta and The Women of Calabash, 01/17/1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Graduate Night With Paula Poundstone, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Tito Puente, 04/09/1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1992 AAU D.C. Body Building Championship, 06/27/1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Global Rhythms International Week, 04/06/1992-04/11/1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Heart Strings, 06/09/1992 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Nina Simone, 06/18/1992 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Griot New York - Garth Fagan Dance, 06/12/1992-06/13/1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Pan Jazz, 04/19/1992 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - D.C. Art Work Dance, 08/05/1992-08/06/1992 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Matthew Sweet "Girlfriend", 1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Christmas Revels, 12/05/1991-12/08/1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Caribbean Extravaganza, 05/16/1992 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Nutcracker, 12/13/1991-12/29/1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Four play, 04/05/1992 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Jay Leno, 09/21/1983 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Nutcracker, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Caligula Camus, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Alvin Ailey Dance, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Clancy Bros. & Tommy Makem, 11/17/1968 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Sonny Rollins, 12/08/1990 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - The Residents, 01/31/1985 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Ronald Twuni Pianist, 01/24/1970 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Alicia de Larrocho Pianist, 11/18/1967 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Marcel Marceau, 02/10/1970-02/11/1970 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Andres Segovia - April 4, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Jose Greco - January 27,28, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Merce Cunninghman Dance, 02/24/1970-02/25/1970 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Martha Graham Dance, 03/04/1976-03/06/1976 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    2 posters
  - The Photographer - Philip Glass, 03/09/1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Growth Factor, Peptide, & Receptors Symphonic, 06/01/1991-06/05/1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 1992 NPC Bodybuilding Championship, 06/06/1992 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Gay Men's Chorus, 06/17/1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Kenny Loggins, 11/22/1991 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Autographed
  - Alice in Wonderland, 02/12/1992 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Czech Version
  - Lodo Dance Ensemble from Croatia, 04/11/1992 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Nashenaz, 01/19/1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Nitzer Ebb, 03/19/1992 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Martin Luther King Dream in Action Convocation, 01/15/1992 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Chinese Folk Dance, 08/02/1992 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Faces of Hope, 04/18/1992 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Mickey Hart, 11/23/1992 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Anita Mui, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Dancers of the Third Age, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Dance Theater of Harlem, 08/05/1992-08/06/1992 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Mercedes Sosa - November 4, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Imperial Bells of China, 04/06/1999-04/09/1989 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Gay Men's Chorus, 06/16/1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - G.W.U. Opening Convocation, 09/09/1988 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - 1990 Cantonese Opera Troupe (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Matthew Sweet, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Bertice Berry, 08/27/1991 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Tom Deluca, 08/24/1991 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Medical Center - IV International Symposium on Neutral Transplants, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Army Band, 05/09/1992 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Posters and LP albums, 1970-1994; RG0055 Series 6; 2.5 Linear feet (Box 2, Flat box 1)
  This series includes performance posters, record albums and cassette tapes of performers. They range in date from 1970-94.
  Formerly ACC# 211.
  - Cassette tape-The King's Men-"It's Testifying Time", 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Cassette tape-America: The United States Air Force Band & Singing Sergeants, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    2 copies
  - Cassette tape-Holly Near "Sky Dances", undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - The Christmas Revels Songbook, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Langstaff, Nancy and John. The Christmas Revels Songbook. Boston: David R. Godine, Publisher, 1985.
  - Record Album-Carol Lynn Pearson and Lex deAzevedo "My Turn on Earth", undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Record Album-Cleve Francis with Billy Pierce "Timeless", 1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Record Album-Dreamgirls, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Record Album-Great Songs of Christmas, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Record Album-Holly Near "Speed of Light", undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Record Album-Lisa Rich "Listen Here", 1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Record Album-Lyle Lovett and his Large Band, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Record Album-Robyn Hitchcock 'n' The Egyptians, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Record Album-The Children "Every Single Day", 1990 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Record Album-The Human League Red "I Need Your Loving", 1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Record Album-The Weavers "Together Again", 1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Record Album-The Wolfe Tones "Across the Broad Atlantic", 1976 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Record Album-The Wolfe Tones "Up the Rebels", undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Record Album-Westworld "Do No Wrong", 1991 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Magnets-GWU Lisner Auditorium-University Series, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Poster-Holly Near and Ronnie Gilbert "Singing with You", undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - T-shirt-Ballet Folklorico De Mexico 40th Anniversary Tour 500 Years of Dance, 1492-1992 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Poster-Betty, January 20-21, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Poster-Martha Graham Dance Company, 3/4/1976-3/6/1976 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Poster-D.C. Amateur Grand Prix Bodybuilding Championships, 6/5/1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Poster-Kate Clinton, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    dated February 25
  - Poster-Festival of Korea, 9/28/1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Poster-Folk Music of Iran Sima Bina, 02/05/1994 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Poster-Ballet National Folklorique de Philipinas-Dir. Ramon A. Obusan, 02/06/1994 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Poster-Ebi Live in Concert, 02/13/1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Poster-Cowboy Junkies with Billy Pilgrim, 02/23/1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Poster-Jazz Vocalist Debbie Mcfarlan, 02/09/1994 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Poster-David Rousseve-Tales of Creole Women, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Poster-Ninth Annual WFMA Benefit Concert, 01/22/1994 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Poster-Lea De Laria with Special Guest Commonbond, 01/20/1994-01/21/1994 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Poster-Gross National Product presents "The Clintoons", 01/29/1994 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Poster-Dance Brazil, 01/15/1994 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Poster-Philadelphia, 12/07/1993 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Poster-The Canterbury Tales, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    Dated November 20
  - Poster-Perry Payne Sings Lesser Known Loesser, 11/03/1993 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Poster-Ustad Vilayat Khan, 09/19/1993 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Poster-Noel Lee, 10/16/1993 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Poster-American Indian Dance Theatre, 10/15/1993-10/17/1993 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Poster-Hungry for Music, 09/17/1993 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Poster-The University of the Philippines Madrigal Singers, 04/28/1993 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Poster-Harry Anderson and the World Magic Summit, 05/01/1993 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Poster-Quilapayun, 06/11/1993 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Poster-Gay Men's Chorus of Washington, 06/19/1993 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Poster-Leonard Cohen, 07/18/1993 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Poster-We Remember Observation of the Birthday of Doctor Martin Luther King, Jr., 01/18/1988 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Poster-The Ecclesia, 06/26/1993 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Poster-Latin Soul featuring Ray Barreto and his Latin Jazz Ensemble, 04/27/1993 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Poster-Teresa Gunn, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
    Dated April 11. 2 copies
  - Poster-Ali Akbar Khan, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Dated February 8
  - Poster-Merce Cunningham and Dance Company, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
    Dated March 16 and 17
  - Poster-Los Kjarkas, 02/17/1989 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Poster-U2 Rattle and Hum, 03/23/1989 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Poster-The Army Soldier Show, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Poster-Annual Celebration in Honor of Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr., 01/16/1989 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Poster-The 1st Laser Show, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
    Dated April 13
  - Poster-Irish Spring Benefit, 04/02/1986 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Poster-Phil Coulters Pops Orchestra of Ireland, 01/07/1987 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Poster-Tantric Rituals by the Gyuto Tantric Monks of Tibet, 04/30/1985 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Poster-Bobcat Goldthwait, undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
    signed
  - Poster-D.C. BodyBuilding Championships, 06/18/1988 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Poster-In Concert Tommy Makem and Liam Clancy, undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Poster-Merce Cunningham and Dance Company, 02/24/1970-02/25/1970 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Poster-Ollantay Andean Music, 07/13/1988 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Poster-Simply Red Men and Women, 11/03/1987 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Poster-Capitol City Jazz Festival, undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
    Dated September 22 to October 1
  - Poster-The Nutcracker, December 13-29, 1991, 12/13/1991-12/29/1991 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Poster-Batcheva Dance Company, undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
    Dated November 12 to 13. 2 copies
  - Poster-Kundrirana Feeling Good, undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Poster-Cloud Gate, undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
    Dated November 4, 5, and 6. 2 copies
  - Poster-Ana Martinez Spanish Flamenco Dance Company, 04/28/1985 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Poster-La Traviata, 11/22/1980-11/23/1980 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Poster-The Burundi National Dance Group, 04/23/1991-04/25/1991 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Poster-Eddie Griffin, undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
    Dated October 16
  - Poster-The Washington Ballet, undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Photo-6 women standing outside in field, undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Photo-Steven Wright, 02/19/1993 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Poster-The Dream in Action, 01/15/1992 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Poster-Cloud Gate Taipei Contemporary Dance Theatre, undated (Box 2, Folder 61)
    Dated November 4-6
  - Poster-Lisner Auditorium program, undated (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Poster-University Honors Convocation, 04/14/1985 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Poster-Raphael Live in Concert, undated (Box 2, Folder 64)
    Dated September 16
  - Poster-Gyuto Monks Tibetan Tantric Choir, 11/16/1988 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Poster-The Princess Bride, 03/31/1988 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Poster-Stars Nite Show, 11/08/1987 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Poster-Dennis Miller, undated (Box 2, Folder 68)
    Dated January 15
  - Poster-The World By Sea, 11/03/1988 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Schedules, 1969-1994; RG0055 Series 7; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes schedules of events at lisner auditorium. They range in date from 1969-94.
  Formerly ACC# 228.
  - Lisner Auditorium schedule, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Lisner Auditorium schedule, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Lisner Auditorium schedule, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Lisner Auditorium schedule, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Lisner Auditorium schedule, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Lisner Auditorium schedule, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Lisner Auditorium schedule, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Lisner Auditorium schedule, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Lisner Auditorium schedule, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Lisner Auditorium schedule, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Lisner Auditorium schedule, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Lisner Auditorium schedule, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Lisner Auditorium schedule, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Lisner Auditorium schedule, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Lisner Auditorium schedule, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Lisner Auditorium schedule, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Lisner Auditorium schedule, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Lisner Auditorium schedule, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Lisner Auditorium schedule, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Lisner Auditorium schedule, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Lisner Auditorium schedule, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Lisner Auditorium schedule, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Lisner Auditorium schedule, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Programs, posters, and photographs, 1993-1994; RG0055 Series 8; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes programs, posters, and photos of performers at Lisner. They range in date from 1993-94.
  Formerly ACC#323
  - Lisner-bookmarks-Des'ree, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Lisner-mail program-Bafochi-The Folkloric Dance Ensemble of Chile, 10/21/1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Lisner-photo-Bill T. Jones, Choreographer, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Lisner-photo and programs-Ljuba Kazarnovskaya and Alla Brosterman, 10/30/1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Lisner-program-Bill T. Jones/Arnie Zane Dance Company and Time magazine, 11/18/1994-11/19/1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Lisner-program-Concert Society at Maryland, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Lisner-program-convocation in honor of the 40th President of the United States, 03/28/1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Lisner-program-Twelfth Mayor's Arts Awards, 03/28/1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Lisner-program-Washington Revels, 12/02/1994-12/11/1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Dec. 2-4 and Dec. 9-11
  - Lisner-program-Washington Soloists Ensemble Benefit Concert, 11/25/1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Lisner-program and poster-Harvest of Harmony featuring Joker's Wild, 11/05/1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Lisner-program and small posters-Ute Lemper In Concert, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Lisner-small poster-Joshua Redman, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Lisner-small poster-Mahendra Kapoor Live, 09/11/1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Lisner-small poster-Spanish Dance Society Performance and Lecture, 10/04/1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Lisner-small poster-Suzanne Westenhoefer, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Lisner-small posters-The Whirling Dervishes, 11/10/1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Posters, 1989-1994; RG0055 Series 9; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 2, Box 1)
  This series includes 157 performance posters from lisner auditorium. They range in date from 1989-94.
  Formerly ACC# 335; numbering of posters is continuous.
  - Celebrate the City, 200 Years 1797-1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bruce Cockburn, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ballet Folklorico de Mexico, 10/01/1994-10/02/1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Ballet Folklorico de Mexico, 10/09/1994-10/11/1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Andrew Cacho, African Drummers and Dancers, 08/06/1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Christmas Revels, 12/02/1994-12/11/1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Dec. 2-4 and 9-11
  - Bafochi, 10/21/1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Inti-illimani, 11/01/1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Ballet Folklorico de Mexico, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Rusted Root, 1994 ca. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    originally dated "194"
  - The Mommies Live, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Dated May 10
  - David Byrne, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - David Byrne, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Potomac All Star Comedy Tour with Dennis Miller, 10/08/1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Potomac All Star Comedy Tour with Dennis Miller, 10/08/1992 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Bertice Berry, 10/27/1992 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Celebration of Van Cliburn, 09/28/1992 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Celebration of Van Cliburn, 09/28/1992 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Celebration of Van Cliburn, 09/28/1992 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Harry Anderson and the World Magic Summit, 05/01/1993 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Shawn Colvin, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - American Indian Dance Theatre, 10/15/1993-10/17/1993 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Michael Nyman Live, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Ottmar Liebert and Luna Negra, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - The Dance Institute of Washington, 08/04/1994-08/05/1994 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Sandra Bernhard, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Dated Oct. 16
  - Sandra Bernhard, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Reverend Jesse Jackson, 02/24/1991 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Geoff Brown, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
    Dated Aug. 29
  - Geoff Brown, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Concrete Blonde, 09/19/1992 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Tom Deluca, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Matthew Sweet, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Branford Marsalis, 06/14/1992 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Dead Can Dance, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Blues Traveler, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Dated Oct. 23
  - George Winston, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Dated Jun. 9-10
  - Christmas Revels, 12/03/1993-12/12/1993 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Dated Dec. 3-5, 10-12
  - KanKouran West African Dance Company, 09/05/1992 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Sheryl Crow, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - D.C. Amateur Grand Prix Bodybuilding Championships, 06/01/1991 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - D.C. Amateur Grand Prix Bodybuilding Championships, 04/30/1994 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Town Hall Meeting Forum on Vaccines for older Adults, 06/01/1994 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - The Best of Mummenschanz, 05/05/1991 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - WMATA (Metro): 8th Annual Employee Awards Ceremony, 06/19/1990 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Calypso Extravaganza, 07/15/1990 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Miss Latin-America Beauty Pageant, 06/29/1990-06/30/1990 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Richard Smallwood Singers, undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Chinese National Performing Art Troupe, 02/14/1991 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Hwa-Shia Goodwill-Mission R.O.C., 10/16/1990 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Hans Choi, 11/12/1992 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Seniorita Festival Latinamericano, 06/29/1990-06/30/1990 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Branford Marsalis, 10/04/1990 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Hunter S. Thompson on "Gonzo Elections", 10/10/1990 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - World Folk Music Association 8th Annual Benefit Concert, 01/09/1993 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Yerachmiel Begun and the Miami Boys Choir, 01/10/1993 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Robert Hunter, undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
    Dated Nov. 7
  - Kate Clinton, undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
    Dated Jan. 25
  - Ballet Folklorico de Mexico, 10/26/1991-10/27/1991 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    Attended by President and Mrs. Bush
  - Richard Smallwood Singers, 07/13/1990 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - WMATA (Metro): 9th Annual Employee Awards Ceremony, 06/19/1991 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Maxi Priest, 12/05/1990 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Maxi Priest, 12/05/1990 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Jinling Art Performance Troupe of China, 10/21/1993 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Miriam Makeba and Hugh Masakela in celebration of the first free elections in South Africa, 02/26/1994 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Miriam Makeba and Hugh Masakela in celebration of the first free elections in South Africa, 02/26/1994 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Trio in Harmony: Gay Men's Chorus, 03/08/1991 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - "Rudy" movie poster, 10/12/1993 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - The Nut-Kracker, undated (Box 1, Folder 69)
    Dated Dec. 18-20
  - Creole Families: Louisiana Zydeco and Jazz, 01/26/1991 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Haris Alexiou and her band, 10/26/1993 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Tommy Makem and Schooner Fare, undated (Box 1, Folder 72)
    Mar. 4
  - Petra Media Production (in Arabic), 06/16/1991 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Irish Spring Benefit, undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
    Dated Apr. 27
  - Nancy Griffith, 03/19/1993-03/20/1993 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Nancy Griffith, 03/19/1993-03/20/1993 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - BoDeans Go Slow Down, 11/22/1993 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Moein in Concert, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Phil Coulter, 12/10/1988 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Youssou N'Dour, undated (Box 1, Folder 80)
    Dated July 1
  - Dvorak's Rusalka with Renee Fleming, 04/18/1993-04/20/1993 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    Performances on Apr. 18 and 20
  - Persian songstress, 02/12/1992 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - KanKouran, 09/04/1993 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Eric Johnson, undated (Box 2, Folder 84)
    Dated Sept. 22
  - Michael Hedges, undated (Box 2, Folder 85)
    Dated Oct. 22
  - Burundi National Dance Group, 04/24/1991 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Cowboy Junkies, 02/23/1994 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Tabu Ley Rochereau, 11/16/1993 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Shahram Nazeri, 01/30/1993 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Great Masters of Classical Persian Music, 10/18/1991 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Gay Men's Chorus of Washington, 07/03/1991 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Pledge Tour, undated (Box 2, Folder 92)
    Dated Oct. 27
  - Suzanne Vega, 01/29/1993 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Miss Black USA Scholarship Pageant, 02/28/1993 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - The Dance Institute of Washington, undated (Box 2, Folder 95)
    Apr. 5-6
  - Masters of Classical Persian Music, 10/18/1991 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - The Asaph Ensemble, undated (Box 2, Folder 97)
    Dated May 20
  - Sweet Honey in the Rock, 04/20/1990 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - The National Heritage Fellowships Celebration and Concert, 09/23/1994 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Rouhollah Khaleghi Orchestra, 03/03/1990 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - University Series, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Awaji Puppet Theatre of Japan, undated (Box 2, Folder 102)
    Dated Feb. 10
  - Le Mystere des Voix Bulgares, undated (Box 2, Folder 103)
    Dated Apr. 7